{"data":[{"question":"The average age at which people begin to need eyeglasses vary considerably.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"at which","b":"begin to need","c":"vary","d":"considerably","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Vary-> varies","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Generally regarded as distinct continents, Europe and Asia are simply vast geography divisions of a larger land mass.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Generally","b":"as","c":"simply","d":"geography","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Geography-> geographic","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"The specific gravity of the water in the great Salt Lake is too great that one cannot sink or completely submerge in it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"specific","b":"too","c":"completely","d":"submerge","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Too-> so","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Did you use to crying so much every night when you were a baby?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Did you use to","b":"crying","c":"every night","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Crying-> cry","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"It has been known for the last two centuries that lightning was a form of electricity.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"It has","b":"the last","c":"was","d":"a form","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Was->is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"The intention of environmentalists is to protect the disappearing spotted owl with the least disruptive to the lumber industry.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"to protect","c":"disappearing","d":"disruptive","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Disruptive-> disruption","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"The common notion that fish is an excellent food improving brain is not supported by any scientific information.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"improving","c":"supported","d":"scientific","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Improving-> to improve","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"His sister told him finish his homework before going to the movies.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"told","b":"finish","c":"homework","d":"going","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Finish-> to finish","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"Not only cigarettes but alcohol is believed to be harmful to one's health.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Not only","b":"but","c":"is believed","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- But-> but also","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"},{"question":"The first step of scientific research is to decide how gather data.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"scientific","b":"is","c":"to decide","d":"gather","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Gather-> to gather","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"36","type":"1"}]}